data = [{"section":"setup","question":"Do you want to<br/> use WordPress?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Don't be silly. Read this.","text":'',"type":"guide","item":"10 reasons why WordPress is great for small business websites","url":"http://www.simplybusiness.co.uk/knowledge/articles/2012/08/wordpress-for-sme/"},
{"section":"setup","question":"Have you chosen<br/> your site name?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Not to worry. Lesson 101 coming up.","text":'',"type":"guide","item":"How to choose the right domain name","url":"http://www.seomoz.org/blog/how-to-choose-the-right-domain-name"},
{"section":"setup","question":"Have you<br/> set up hosting?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Easier than it sounds.  Check this out.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to set up hosting","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/N-Hqw-OkQwI' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe><p>If you already have your domain name, but want to host it elsewhere, check out this <a href='http://www.thesitewizard.com/domain/point-domain-name-website.shtml' target='_blank'>simple guide</a>. <br/>For ease, we recommend HostGator, but if you want to check out other options, <a href='http://yoast.com/articles/wordpress-hosting/' target='_blank'>try these</a>."},
{"section":"setup","question":"Is WordPress<br/> installed?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Wordpress makes this super-easy.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to install Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/k7xc9oKCjZk' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe><p>If you&rsquo;re using a different hosting company, check with them how to install Wordpress.</p>"},
{"section":"setup","question":"Have you set up an email for your site?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Have a look at this.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to set up an email account for your domain","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/_WIHRrzp6y8' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe><p>If you&rsquo;re using a hosting company other than HostGator, check with them how to set up email.</p>"},
{"section":"setup","question":"Do you know how to install plugins?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"It will come in handy.  Watch this.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to install Wordpress plugins","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/bPPa9eBagmQ' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"design","question":"Chosen a design<br/> for your site?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"A visual treat<br/> coming up.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to install your Wordpress theme","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/uTSDip7m6zU' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"design","question":"Know how to make good permalinks?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Let's do it now then.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to set up user friendly permalinks","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/JJK_-QhLlEg' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"design","question":"Have you decided what pages you need?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"This one's worth some thought.","text":'',"type":"guide","item":"10 pages every small business website should have","url":"http://www.bourncreative.com/website-design-tips-10-pages-every-small-business-website-should-have"},
{"section":"design","question":"Do you know how<br/> to create pages?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"You will in a minute.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to create pages in Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/IbXjmnyvYCQ' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"design","question":"Know how to make<br/> a contact form?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Best get on that then.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing your contact form plugin","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/s3CutJIUZS4' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"design","question":"Is your site navigation in order?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"No time like<br/> the present.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Menus in Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/N8FdT9tn_L8' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"content","question":"Do you know how to add content?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"There's nothing to it.  Promise.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to add content to pages in Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/0u4TOksfGZw' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"content","question":"Know how to<br/> install widgets?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Fortune favours<br/> the brave!","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to manage widgets in Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/5WMNUOe-g64' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"content","question":"Have you set up<br/> your blog?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Then step right<br/> this way&hellip;","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to set up your Wordpress blog","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/TzFvgmOu4DA' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe><p>Once your blog is ready, set up your RSS feed by following <a href='http://www.wpbeginner.com/beginners-guide/step-by-step-guide-to-setup-feedburner-for-wordpress/' target='_blank'>this guide</a></p>"},
{"section":"content","question":"Will you be the only site administrator?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Ah, you've brought<br/> the cavalry","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to set up multiple users in Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ngj99vwlkzk' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"content","question":"Have you set up<br/> a Gravatar?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Fear not - we'll<br/> explain all&hellip;","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"How to set up your Gravatar","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/dP_Y4Jh8m1A' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"content","question":"Have you added<br/> social buttons?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Alright, time to<br/> get social!","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing the Shareaholic plugin","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/37JJuQAqtEY' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"behind","question":"Do you want your website to be slow?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Stupid question really.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing WP Super Cache","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/qz22DRHpdbY' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"behind","question":"Is your website<br/> backed up?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"You should probably<br/> do that.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing the DB Backup plugin","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/NKnm2LM7pfk' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"behind","question":"Do you love SPAM?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Don't worry, we've got your back.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing the Akismet plugin","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/DqzfiErf8Sw' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"behind","question":"Got Analytics<br/> installed?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Would be a smart<br/> thing to do.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing Google Analytics in Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/y5QE5bH4Ado' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"behind","question":"Know how to update Wordpress?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"You'll need this<br/> in due course.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Updating Wordpress","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/bt-7sJ8APwc' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"},
{"section":"behind","question":"Set up an alert for broken links?","answer1":"Yes","answer2":"No","response":"Not nearly as scary<br/> as it sounds.","text":'',"type":"screencast","item":"Installing the Broken Link Checker plugin","url":"<iframe width='853' height='480' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/ccGAfk2CFbQ' frameborder='0' allowfullscreen></iframe>"}]


function generateLists(col){
	// build article list:
	aList = $('#'+col+' .group');
	aList.empty();
	var i = 0,
		row = 'rowOne';
	var listItem = '';
	$.each(data,function(){
		if (data[i]['section'] == col){
			if (data[i]['question'] != ''){
				
				listItem += '<li class="item '+row+'" id="'+data[i]['section']+i+'">';
					listItem += '<div class="query"><h5>'+data[i]['question']+'</h5></div>';
				
					listItem += '<span class="proceed">'+data[i]['answer1']+'</span>';
					listItem += '<a href="#" class="button">'+data[i]['answer2']+'</a>';
					listItem += '<div class="response">';
						listItem += '<a href="#" class="closeResponse close"><span class="hide">Close</span></a>';
						listItem += '<h6>'+data[i]['response']+'</h6>';
						if(data[i]['type'] == "screencast") {
							listItem += '<a href="#" data-id="'+i+'" class="resource '+data[i]['type']+'">'+data[i]['item']+'</a>';
						} else {
							listItem += '<a href="'+data[i]['url']+'" class="resource '+data[i]['type']+'" target="_blank">'+data[i]['item']+'</a>';
						}
					listItem += '</div>';
				listItem += '</li>';
			}
		}
		i++;
		if(i%3 == 0) row = 'rowTwo';
		if(i%6 == 0) row = 'rowOne';
	});
	aList.append(listItem);
}